噢  嘿
Oh, hey.
听说你感觉不太舒服
Heard you weren't feeling very well.
啊  是的  大概是虫子什么的吧
Oh, yeah. Must be a bug or something.
唔  我希望你明天对阵灰熊队的比赛能发挥正常啊
Mm, well, I hope you'll be okay for the game against the grizzlies tomorrow.
我觉得经过一晚上的睡眠应该能恢复好的
I'm pretty sure I'll be fine after a good night's sleep.
嗯哼  要我给你拿点姜汁汽水么
Mm-hmm. Can I get you some ginger ale?
或是一些咸饼干
Or some crackers?
呃  不用了  我感觉挺好的
Um, no, I'm... I'm fine.
而且我的床在这边
I'm also over here.
你在找什么呢
What are you looking for?
哦
Oh!
有点头脑发热吧
A fever.
哎呀呀
Aww!
嘿  妈  妈
Hey, mom. Mom.
咋了
Hmm?
你在找丽芙的那双漂亮鞋子  对不
You're looking for Liv's perfect pumps, aren't you?
什么  才不是呢
What? No.
不  我  我根本停不住对鞋的思念
No, I... I can't stop thinking about them.
我想立马穿上
I want to slip 'em on.
哪怕只穿一个趾头  我就是想过过瘾
Even just a toe. I just need a taste.
呃  那个  其实高跟鞋不在这里
Mm, yeah, well, they're actually not in here.
我刚看见丽芙来过找了一轮了
I just saw Liv coming and looking for them.
所以我要是看见了的话会通知你的
So if I see them, I will let you know.
但是  嘿  妈妈  与此同时
But... hey, mom. In the meantime,
你或许应该想想你的尊严该穿在哪里
you might want to slip on a size 10 dose of dignity.
你说得对
You're right.
我不知道我怎么像着了魔一样
I don't know what's gotten into me.
如果你胆敢告诉丽芙我来过这儿  你就会
If you tell Liv I was here, and you will be...
我到底是怎么了
what's wrong with me?
嗨  宝贝们
Hi, girls.
我刚骗走了我妈
I just lied to my mom.
还是关于鞋子的
About shoes.
哈  而且我根本就不在乎
Ha! And I don't even care.